tuitalk.com 2010-11-28

# Free Internet Online Phone Calls TUITALK

## tuitalk™ SERVICE PRIVACY POLICY

tuitalk respects the privacy and the confidentiality of your personal data, and communications content. tuitalk is a brand of ARGELA-USA, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“tuitalk”, “we” or “us”). 

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) is designed to assist you with understanding how tuitalk uses and safeguards the information you provide in using the tuitalk services, the tuitalk client application and the tuitalk website (collectively, the “tuitalk Services”).

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy describes tuitalk’s use of Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we collect when you use the tuitalk Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of your Personal Information that is collected by third parties that tuitalk does not own or control or that do not support tuitalk in providing the tuitalk Services.

“Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

“Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. 

We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy from the visitors of our website, and from the users of the tuitalk Services.

BY USING THE tuitalk™ SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE tuitalk™ SERVICES, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED BY US IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY. BY USING THE tuitalk™ SERVICES, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO AND THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN SUCH OTHER COUNTRIES.

## Information Collected

tuitalk collects information about you (including Personal Information) as follows:

(a) If you register for a tuitalk account, we collect Personal Information about you such as your name, street address, telephone number, email address;

(b) In connection with your registration, we also collect other information about you on a voluntary basis, such as your sex or your hobbies, which will be used to select relevant advertisements;

(c) When you use the tuitalk Services, certain information will be collected passively via technology, such as you IP address;

(d) In connection with your usage of the tuitalk Services, certain usage-related information is collected, such as the used calling minutes, number of SMSs sent, or duration of calls made. We also collect information about the history of your tuitalk Service use (e.g., calls made by time and day) and the name and telephone number of the persons that you call or send SMS to using the tuitalk Services;

(e) The tuitalk Services collect any other information you decide to provide, like review comments and ratings of advertisements posted at tuitalk website;

(f) When you contact us by sending us an e-mail or using one of our webforms, we will collect your name and the content of your communication and any information that you choose to attach to it.

## Information Collected Via Technology

Cookies are pieces of information that the tuitalk software may store on your computer's hard drive in order to help us to recognize you or your or preferences. tuitalk may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). tuitalk’s cookies may contain identifying information. Cookies enable tuitalk to gain information about your use of the tuitalk Services. This information may be analyzed by third parties on our behalf. The Help option on the toolbar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please bear in mind that some personalized services may not be available if you choose to disable cookies.

## Personal Information From Other Sources

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone or fax, or from third parties that provide services for us in connection with the tuitalk Services. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via our tuitalk Services.

## Use Of Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting information is to provide you with a secure and customized experience of the tuitalk Services. tuitalk collects and processes,information about you to provide you with the tuitalk Services, in particular, but not limited to, to convey the communications you make by means of your use of the tuitalk application and tuitalk Services; provide you with customer support and troubleshoot problems; inform you about service updates; request feedback or participation in on-line surveys; verify your identity; customize, measure, and improve tuitalk application and tuitalk Services content and layout; invoice our services with advertising partners and other third parties that help us offering the tuitalk Services; organize and perform tuitalk’s marketing or promotional operations/offers, contests, games and similar events; and to enforce our Terms of Service and fight against fraud; and convey your feedback on advertisements to advertisers to improve the quality and content of advertisements.

We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with notifications related to your use of the tuitalk Services, such as electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, should you request to receive such communications from us. 

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may also create Anonymous Information on how you use the tuitalk Services. We may use this Anonymous Information for internal purposes, such as analyzing usage patterns so that we may enhance our tuitalk Services, and we also reserve the right to use and disclose any Anonymous Information at our discretion.

## Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not use or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so. 

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers and suppliers who work on behalf of or with us to provide you with the tuitalk Services and some of the services and features of the tuitalk Services and to help us communicate with our users. Examples of such services include communicating with you via e-mail, invoice certain joint services, improve content and quality of the advertisements, and/or providing customer service or fulfillment services for us. However, these service providers and suppliers do not have any independent right to use this information except as to help us providing the tuitalk Services.

Please be aware that, notwithstanding the abovementioned, in the event that an authority lawfully requests that tuitalk retains and/or provides information (including Personal Information), communications content and/or traffic data, tuitalk will provide all reasonable assistance and information to fulfil this request.

Although we currently do not have a any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. 

In the event Argela-USA goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Argela-USA or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to Argela-USA sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances.

We may disclose information we have collected from and about you (including Personal Information) if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service, EULA, and Privacy Policy; or (c) to protect and defend the rights or property of us, the visitors and users of our tuitalk Services, or third parties.

## Security

tuitalk has put in place commercially reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no company, including tuitalk, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

## Communications with you

Unsubscribe instructions will accompany each newsletter or promotional communication you receive from us.

We will send you strictly service-related announcements (such as, but not limited to, notices of any updates to our tuitalk Services, Terms of Service, EULA, or Privacy Policy) when we believe it is necessary to do so. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature, but if you do not wish to receive these announcements, you have the option to terminate your Account, which involves termination of the tuitalk Terms of Service. You understand that any termination of your Account and the tuitalk Terms of Service involves deletion of your Account information from our live databases and all the information and data stored for such Account in the tuitalk Services. tuitalk will not have any liability whatsoever to you for any termination of your Account or related deletion of you information or data. 

tuitalk may from time to time ask you to provide information on your experiences which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time in any obligation to provide any of such information. Any and all information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback forms on our website or any survey that you accept to take part in is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the tuitalk Services.

tuitalk may also use email or the tuitalk application to keep you up to date with news about the tuitalk Services unless you have opted out of receiving this information.

When we delete information that we have collected from or about you, it will be deleted from our active databases but may remain in our archives.

## Links to Other Web Sites

The tuitalk Services may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by tuitalk. The provision of such links is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such websites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other websites. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to any outside websites.

## Privacy of Minors

We do not intentionally collect or maintain information in the tuitalk Services from those visitors and Users of the tuitalk Services who are under 13 years old.

## Modifying the Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement is a living document. As part of the tuitalk Website Terms & Conditions, this Privacy Policy is subject to occasional amendment, in accordance with the terms of the tuitalk Website Terms & Conditions.

## Your Rights 

You have the right to access and, where relevant, to rectify your personal data, provided that your identity can be verified. If you would like to exercise your right to view, correct, complete or remove your personal data, please contact tuitalk. Within a reasonable period of time and upon verification of your identity and to the extent your request is legitimate, tuitalk will fulfil your request, provided tuitalk will not act contrary to applicable legislation by fulfilling your request. 

You may also oppose to the processing by tuitalk of your personal data. However, in this case, tuitalk will not be in a position to provide the tuitalk client. You can exercise your right to oppose to the processing detailed in the Privacy Statement by contacting [tuitalk_delete_me@tuitalk.com](mailto:tuitalk_delete_me@tuitalk.com)

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at 2350 Mission College Blvd, Suite 360, Santa Clara, California 95054.

© tuitalk– Last revised: January 2008
